trishtech.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting and using TrishTech.com. Your privacy on the Internet is very important to us. At TrishTech.com, we want to make your online experience satisfying and safe.

The following privacy statement discloses the privacy policy practices for TrishTech.com.

Collection of personal information

We do not collect any personally identifiable information from you which may include your name, address, email address or other contact information without your consent.

When you contact us using the “Contact Us” form, your emails messages are not shared with any third party. Any replies sent are sent only to the email address that you have used to contact us.

When you leave comments, you may use your real name, email address and website address all of which gets associated with your comments. Your email address stays invisible to other visitors of TrishTech.com. We do not sell or share this information with any third party. We do not associate or store IP addresses with the comments.

We use many social networks for TrishTech.com using static links only. When you click on these links, you are taken to the third-party social networking sites that have their own privacy policies. We do not record any user activity or interaction on these social networking sites.

Advertisements displayed on this website often use cookies and web beacons to collect data in order to better serve the ads. You can use your web browser tools to block them.

Third party content

Articles on this website may include content hosted on third party websites such as videos, images and PDF files. These websites, the content of which has been embedded on TrishTech.com, may collect data about you, use tracking cookies, and trace your interaction with the embedded content. This is exactly same as if you have visited those websites.

Third party advertising

We use the Google Adsense program to serve third party advertisements to you when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services of interest to you. Some of these advertisements make use of the Google DART cookie. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

Analytics

We use Google Analytics on our website to collect information about website visits. We have configured Google Analytics to use the lowest period of time for which data that is collected is associated with cookies and user identifiers, and the time period does not reset on new activity. You can read Google Analytics privacy policy for more information: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.

Our web hosting company, GoDaddy, collects aggregate data in the server logs automatically when a user visits the site.

What rights you have over your data

If you have have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. Note that we need to be able to link data to you, for instance, by your email address.

Your consent

By using this site, you consent to our privacy policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this website. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed a your consent to those changes.

Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: admin@trishtech.com.

_(This privacy policy was last modified on 22nd May, 2018)_
